LOURDES CASTRO

USER INTERFACE & EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

CONTACT

- lourdes@uxcastro.com
- linkedin.com/in/lourdes-castro in

UX SKILLS

- User Research /
- Information Architecture

 ✓
 - Wireframing <
 - User Interface Design 🗸
 - Prototyping ✓
 - User Testing <
 - Spontaneity <

DESIGN SKILLS

- Graphic Design
 - Art Direction 🗸
- Conceptual development 🗸
 - Sketching <
 - Illustration <
 - Branding \
 - Typography <

TOOLS

- Adobe C.S. (PS | AI | ID | XD) ✓
 - Office S. (Word | Excell)
- Wordpress | Divi | Mailchimp 🗸
 - Sketch <
- Balsamic | Prottapp | Invision √
 - Power Point / Keynote √

OTHER KNOWLEDGE

- 3D Basic Level ✓
- Video edition Basic Level 🗸

HOBBIES

- Traveler <
- Films V.O. √
- Yoga & Conscious feeding instagram | "_lurca" | "To be, to do, to have"
 - Photography unsplash.com/@_lurca | "I love sharing"

PROFILE

A self-taught UI turned UX Designer passionate for problem-solving and delighted to create the best digital experience. User-centered design processes and methods to achieve the user s needs. Ready to be part of a project that matters and join a team that places user experience and user interface design as a top priority in their business goals.

EXPERIENCE

Currently | UX/UI Designer at "Buleboo Estudio"

User Center Design & Creative Thinker

2014-19 | Art Director at "Nuvenova". Freelancer

UI & UX design for clients' projects needs

²⁰¹⁰⁻¹⁴ | UI Designer & Programmer at "Eukleia". London

E-learning Project development

2008-09 | Art director "Young and Rubicam"

Covering clients' advertising needs

EDUCATION

Currently | Studying UX Designer Specialitation Course. Career Foundry school

2009-10 | Management and design E-Learning & B- Learning courses.
Online | UNED (London)

2004-09 | Graduate in Fine Arts | Complutense University. Madrid

2002-04 | Imaging Technician. Puerta Bonita Center. Madrid

VOLUNTEERISM

06-09/19 | UI & UX at "Kyosei Training Centre". Tanzania | Africa

05-09/19 | UI & UX at "Res Project". Remote

03-07/19 | Graphic designer at "Aeon for Ocean". Remote

O T H E R I N F O R M A T I O N

RES PROJECT

CO-Founder UX & UI Responsibilities Currently

ERASMUS PROGRAM

HAWK Fakultät Bauen und Erhalten. Hildesheim 2008. 10 Months

LANGUAGES

Spanish
Native

English
Level C1

German
Level B1